<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE terms SYSTEM "https://resources.jetbrains.com/writerside/1.0/glossary.dtd">
<terms>
    <term name="session_token">A uuid which references a user's login session, of the form session_[uuidv4].</term>
    <term name="Provider Login Payload">Used to Authenticate a user with a given provider. Made up of a Provider ID, Provider Type, and other Metadata.</term>
    <term name="Allocator">An allocator is responsible for increasing or decreasing game server capacity on specific platform or provider. An allocator may start/stop a process, a container, or make API calls to external services.</term>
    <term name="JMESPath">JMESPath is a query language for JSON. It is used in the Catena match broker and server manager for filtering matches by their properties.</term>
    <term name="services list">The list of service names or group names to include/exclude when building and starting a Catena node. It may be specified in the configuration or on the command line.</term>
    <term name="game server">Usually hosted in a cloud environment using a client/server model, this is your game logic responsible for players, world simulation and gameplay.</term>
    <term name="backend platform">The non-game server portions of your game, usually supporting things like matchmaking, parties, accounts and inventory.</term>
    <term name="fleet manager">A service or tool responsible for allocating and managing a collection of game servers.</term>
    <term name="session resolver">A session resolver is responsible to returning the current session ID, typically from a header or request metadata.</term>
    <term name="session store accessor">An interface that provides consistent methods to create and (in)validate sessions and read/write session data.</term>
    <term name="matchmaking strategy">The algorithm used to make matches which may apply rules related to game modes, team size, player properties, etc.</term>
    <term name="infrastructure provider">A cloud provider (like AWS) responsible for creating the actual servers and infrastructure catena will run on.</term>
</terms>